Friends with brews friends with brews what I have something here called timecode. I have to see what this is
Well, it's good to know that we haven't edited in any way
I will edit it in some way
But I won't tell anybody that I did as as of the time when that guy was claiming that
Well, I was gonna say as of the time that we're recording this it has not yet been edited in any way
All right
Let's talk about our brews because we always give our brews the short shrift and I'm not talking about the brews that my
Running buddy who also is a krav maga buddy sent me because he sent me a nice picture of a bruised forearm because he was doing
Knife defenses last night in krav not that kind of bruise
That was a pretty dull knife if all it did was bruise his arm
Well, I'm gonna say is you don't coward catch the knife you catch the attackers wrist
Instead of the knife because it means less hackers. No good
Well, the idea is to be better than your attacker. So yes, relatively speaking. The attacker is no good. Anyway, what are you drinking Scott?
Well, I've got two things number one. I have a coffee
I have a Trailhead Sunbreak morning blend and it's actually not the better coffee that I have in my coffee
Cupboard, but it is the one that I have not had on the show before so I'm having that and I do like it
It's pretty good. It's all right. It's weird.
I think that the pandemic did something to the local coffee roasters.
I think that whatever supplies,
whatever coffee they're able to get has changed in some way. For example,
Happy Cup used to be our preferred roaster, local roaster.
We don't drink Happy Cup anymore because their coffees don't taste the same to
us anymore. And Trailhead is kind of that way.
When we first started drinking Trailhead, it was way, way, way,
way our favorite. And now I find it easier to brew a slightly bitter cup than I would
like. Let's put it that way. And I don't remember that having been a problem in the past.
Do you think there's any chance that your taste buds have maybe COVID changed your taste
buds? Maybe you taste different. Sure. It's quite possible.
COVID changed both of our taste buds in a way that we both agree on what has changed
with the coffee. Very unlikely.
possible and extremely unlikely.
Pretty.
I can believe that we both got COVID and that our taste buds changed.
What are you going to use for a bleep sound?
You just said pretty much.
And we, yeah, but that's not appropriate right now.
Right now you need my old coffee grinder.
Remember that when we used that on, yeah, we're going to, I'll, I'll, I'll send you
a, that hurts the ears, right?
Well you can mute it down.
You can mute it down.
Yeah.
I like that.
Now tell me about your coffee.
Uh, I'm not drinking coffee yet.
I am currently drinking a tea. I'm pushing the brews boundary, sir. I am drinking.
Oh, that's right. This is the Etsy tea.
Well, no, it's not. But when I did search for it, the number one result on this actually
comes up on Etsy, which I found. I didn't realize that Etsy has, Etsy is just a marketplace
now. I thought it was like for handcrafted goods and stuff, but you can just find anything
on Etsy, apparently. Including tea from my local Wegmans. Well, I don't know, it came
from the local one, but tea from Wegmans supermarket chain. So I am drinking Wegmans gingerbread
flavored tea and I like it. It's a black tea. It has some like caramelly notes. I'm trying
to describe like the way to, I'm describing like the mouth feel. It's got a very smooth
mouth feel to it more than the flavor.
You're sure that's not just your COVID mouth?
I mean, it could be COVID the same as you and your wife's. So yeah, that's possible.
I'm sure if you drank it, you would feel the exact same way because of the same COVID.
You used to have a very rough mouth, but now COVID smoothed it out for you.
It's smoothed over the palate. It's great. It's great. So...
Your FaceTime call has got a lag between the mouth movement and the...
Yeah, there's a slight delay between the audio and the video that I've never noticed before.
If I recall, yours did that last time we recorded, which was kind of funny. So it was disconcerting.
at first but then it was fine. I'm curious if I shut off my video and restart it if that
fixes things. No don't touch a thing. But if I do yeah if I do that'll mess things up I'm sure.
Yeah don't touch a thing. Anyway so my plan is to move on to another brew after this. I haven't
decided if it's going to be a beer or a coffee but I have a new decaf coffee to audition as well.
Yeah well I've already decided what my next one's going to be and I'm going to get it ready for you
right now. Well you can get it ready but but don't tell us yet we want to be
surprised. Your listener wants to be surprised. So what's going on lately with
Scott? Are we still talking Mastodon these days? Are we Mastodon't? What's
what's the deal? Oh no I'm using Mastodon. I'm barely using Twitter. In fact we
this podcast now has a friends with brews Mastodon account. Friends W
brews at appdot.net. It's kind of weird. Okay. Bear with me. A P P D O T .net. Don't
ask me why. There's reasons, but don't ask me why.
This is why Mastodon will not succeed. Oh man. That's funny.
This was because this server was started by a bunch of people that used to be on appdot.net
ADM.net. And that confused me because when you sent me a link to your Mastodon post recently,
a toot, but apparently they're not toots anymore, I guess.
Now they're posts again because people rightly pointed out that toot was the dumbest thing.
It sounds like Bart Simpson. Exactly. But my thought was when you sent something on
appdot.net, I was like, wait, I thought appdot.net was its own thing. That's Mastodon? I was
confused. I thought, you know, and then, and then Siracusa was talking about appdot.net and
You know how it came and went and stuff and now you've just clarified it. So thank you. I am drinking an Nikasi Sleigh'r
Winter ale how do you spell that?
Just like I spelled it in the notes s L e I G H
apostrophe R
I know that's why I asked you to spell it though because our listener can't see the show notes
I'm gonna pour it in the I mean we might publish the show notes and it may show up on friends with brews calm
Or friends w brews on appdot.net.
Friends with apps and dot nets.
Friends with apps dot brews. Friends with brews apps dot net. So I have, as we discussed,
set up two
Mastodon accounts, just grab your own name. I'm Paradigm at InfoSec.Exchange
and I'm also Nikolaidis at InfoSec.Exchange.
You're at Nikolaidis at Infosec.Exchange.
I'm @nikolaidis@infosec.exchange and I'm @paradigm@...
preceding the @, it's just, it's whatever. I'm @paradigm and @nikolaidis on infosec.exchange.
That's where you can find me.
But just for the listener, first of all, we have links on our website at friendswithbrews.com.
Go to the friends page, the links are there. And if you go to the subscribe page or the footer of
any page on the site, our friends will be here. Mastodon account link is there. But
yeah, so if you go to in a web browser, if you go to info sec dot exchange, instead of
typing slash Nikolaidis, you have to type slash at Nikolaidis. That's bizarre, but okay.
That's how Mastodon works. I find Mastodon works bizarrely and that's okay. Yep. So I've
been listening to you or reading your, your posts in our friends with beer friends with
with brews stuff. But I have not taken any other, other real actions on Mastodon yet.
I have not even installed or downloaded any Mastodon clients.
Nor have you put in a profile picture yet.
Nor have I put in a profile. But what I did do is I went to movetodon.org and I logged
in. I authenticated with Twitter. I sound like I've been drinking beer, but I haven't.
I authenticated with Twitter and then I authenticated with Mastodon and I let it tell me, here are
all these people you follow on Twitter and here are all of their equivalents on Mastodon.
Oh my God, I need a don't cross the stream sound clip.
That's what I got to get for next time.
So almost exactly 10% of the people I follow on Twitter have been moved over to Mastodon
and almost all of them are security people.
So I did use this as an opportunity to prune several of them though.
There are people like, I'm just not interested anymore.
Yeah.
Well, you know, if you just, you just take off, like it's like, you know, do a plant.
If you just do like the finger here, like the others will continue to grow around.
So it's not, it shouldn't hurt that bad.
But I did prune.
I don't remember if we talked about this, I bought an Aero garden a couple months back
And I now am growing my own lettuce and dill and basil at home, indoors.
That's why you kept sending me pictures of dill pickles.
Yes, exactly.
No, I never sent you a picture of a dill pickle.
Peter's lonely today.
Never once have I sent you a picture of a pickle dill or otherwise.
Okay.
So let me talk about my beer for just a minute before we go on because we tend to give short
shrift to our brews.
Hmm.
And this is not just a podcast about friends.
It is also about brews.
we should talk about the ruse. Right, so they claim... With our friends. What do they claim?
They claim that it's a limited release and they're right about that.
Roasty toffee malty. I would say it's pretty accurate. It's not super sweet. I don't know
what it is about winter ales, but they tend to be slightly... just ever so slightly bitter. And this
one fits that mold. Okay. I didn't say it has mold, I said it fits that mold. It sounds disgusting if
if it's got mold.
Yeah. Roasty toffee, malty mold.
So no, it's pretty good.
It's not-
Tasting notes.
Notes of mold.
If your family is standing in front of the door
and you have to fight your way out to get to the store
to get this beer and someone in your family
is going to get injured, it's not worth that.
Or especially if you're going to get injured,
it's not worth that.
But it's a good beer.
Don't fight to get injured.
Right. Got it.
Don't fight an angry mob, whether they're family
or otherwise, to get this beer.
But it's pretty good though.
It's a decent winter ale, I would say.
Don't fight a mob, angry or otherwise, to get this.
No, no, no, no.
Don't fight an angry mob, family or otherwise.
How does that, oh, family or otherwise, got it.
How does that compare to well if I was desperate?
This is better than well if I was desperate.
Okay, okay, good.
'Cause I chose this willingly,
knowing that I'd had it before.
I am thinking that we should probably modify
our review scale.
Oh, no.
So instead of like one star or a th-
We're just doing thumbs up and thumbs down right right see that's the problem. There are no thumb sideways icons
I would have to draw my own. I think we might need a thumb sideways icon and the label should be well if I was desperate
Because I would drink it like there's thumbs down is thumbs down means. I'm not drinking this again
I would not drink this again. I would just drink this again
If I was desperate, you know see right now thumbs down doesn't necessarily mean I wouldn't drink it again
But what it means is I I well, how can it not I?
Think it means no, I wish you would you buy it again. I guess not. I don't know
I think thumbs down should mean I'm not gonna drink it. I think we need
you know, I'd say
Thumbs up. Well, here's the other, you know, we could give two thumbs up. No, but then we're basically back into stars
Well, wait Netflix though. I did notice Netflix now has a I don't like this
like this and then two thumbs up for love this
Hmm, so Netflix has gone back into like love don't like like love
See that's the problem is whenever you have a rating system and you're like this rating system is too arbitrary
There's too many levels of rating. This is dumb. Let's simplify it. And then when you get it simplified, you're like
There's no nuance in this rating system. I can't believe it. It's terrible exactly
Maybe we'll just stay with thumbs up and thumbs down and say if I was desperate in the comments, that's true. Yes
Yeah, if I was desperate that should have been the name of this podcast if I was desperate if
No, but these are good. I'm hoping these are gonna be good beers
episode if I was desperate
Okay, isn't the correct way to say that if I were desperate
Mmm. I don't know that that is true actually so
I'm not certain. I am not certain unclear Google grammar
Does why doesn't Google have a Google grammar you can check out grammar girl. I'm sure she's is she on mastadon yet
I don't know. I actually I think she is but so you are obviously down with you know
Mastadu as opposed to mastadon't yeah, that doesn't mean
Because just because I'm using it and liking it doesn't mean that I think it's going to be a Twitter replacement for everybody
I didn't say that you did say no. I'm talking to the listener. We have those maybe I know
but you may make it sound like I just said, "So you think that Mastodon is going to be a Twitter replacement for everybody?"
Well, yes, Peter, I do. In fact, I think it already is and the people on Twitter are just too dumb to know it.
That's so funny because I feel the exact same way.
You know what's weird though? When I do peek at Twitter again,
I feel weird about the fact that a lot of people that I followed there are still using Twitter as though nothing's happened.
Hmm. I don't know how to feel about the fact that I feel that way because maybe they're right and maybe I'm wrong, but I...
I'm telling you right now, not only is the Elon Musk thing going on, but it's not just an illusion that
The creepy people are more in force over there. They're definitely more in force. There's definitely more of them
They're definitely commenting on more things. It's definitely harder to avoid them than it was
Yep, and I just don't feel good about using Twitter as though nothing's happening
And yet a lot of people that I followed over there are and I get it
I understand why but I also don't understand why I'm very divided on that. Yeah. Yep
I am concerned that you know
Musk has made it his actions and his veiled and not so veiled way of saying that essentially he's you know
Gonna turn Twitter into an alt-right platform. Well, he's bringing that he's unbanning all the crappy people. Yeah. Yeah
Endorsing DeSantis, you know, okay. Well, at least we know now
It's funny that he banned the artist formerly known as... what was the artist formerly known as?
What's Ye's name?
Kanye?
Oh really? I didn't even know Ye changed his name.
Is that how you pronounce Ye?
I have no idea.
See, I'm assuming that Kanye calls himself that for the end of his name.
But he's also fairly religious at this point in a very extreme way.
And I also thought he might be using the... in certain languages the name Jesus is pronounced Ye.
"Yay, yay-su, yay, yay-su-su, yay-su."
Interesting.
Like in Japanese, it's "yesu-ki-ri-suto."
"Hay-zus."
No, that's not Chinese.
Huh.
No.
"yesu-ki-ri-suto," yeah, I get that.
No, I assume it's the end of his name, but knowing his ego, it just occurred to me.
So anyway, I noticed that he didn't ban him again.
He did ban him when he started saying he liked Hitler and he liked Nazis, but that was after
he'd already personally insulted Musk. And I do have to wonder, like other people were
like, oh, it's good to know that Musk does have some limits. And I'm like, this isn't
a fair test case because he, he gave Musk an excuse to ban him after he had personally
insulted Musk. When did that happen? Exactly. Though, when, when was the week? Cause I'm
not following, I'm not following it. I'm not either, but I see, I see enough other people
that's following you. Right. So I have not been using Twitter much at all. Like the only
time I do is like when you've been sending me a couple links here and there to some folks
who are still on Twitter. Have I been? A couple. It's not like whenever the last time you did,
that was the last time I was on Twitter. Other than logging into, you know, enable move to
dawn. Oh, I think I sent you a couple things about Elon Musk. Yeah. Yeah, exactly. But
other than that, I haven't been using it. Um, since I wiped my iPhone and started from
scratch, I certainly have not installed the Twitter app on it yet. I wipe my phone at
at least once a day, because I don't like fingerprints on my screen.
That's that's good. That's good. Especially in COVID times, you know,
it's good to, you know, keep things clean and stuff. Yeah, sure.
Is that the kind of wipe you're talking about? Well, we'll talk about,
we'll talk about your wipe. No, you don't want to talk about your wipe.
I don't. That was covered on the blurring the lines podcast.
So we're going to keep it.
Whatever you do. I think what you said on blurring the lines, and I quote is,
don't flush your wipe down the toilet.
No, you can flush the wipe down the toilet.
Don't flush your wiped phone down the toilet is what I said.
There's a difference. You're quoting me out of context here.
Yeah, but it's the municipal facilities that get all upset when you flush your
wipes down the...
You think how upset they're going to be when a phone comes down the pipes.
My God, we thought the fatberg was bad.
Oh my God. Hey, I am about out of tea,
so I would like to refresh my brew. Here's the question.
Since we're doing the split recording,
Do I stop and we restart or do I just record silence and you entertain our dear listener while I step away?
I can get rid of silence a lot easier that I can line up an ex recording. Oh, I'm supposed to entertain you
Yes, I will entertain you. So yeah, I am using Mastodon
I think that I already see some subsiding of what I thought was going to be a culture war between
people that have been using Mastodon for a long time and were
very
hardcore about content warnings for
thing. And I'm not the only person who thinks that the content warnings have been a little excessive.
Like, I've seen people content warning things that I can't figure out why.
People content warning pictures of them making eye contact with the camera.
Which... I...
I don't know, it's weird. Like, on the one hand I get it at some level,
but on the other hand there have to be some limits. Like, in human interaction,
That's how we communicate with each other and I get that some people aren't good with it. I don't know. It's weird. I
Don't know. I think that the culture on Mastodon is already changing and I think I'm pretty okay with that
I think it has to if it's going to be adopted by more mainstream people
Now what I don't know is if it will ever be adopted by a lot of mainstream people like I'm thinking a
lot of us are on Twitter to follow journalists and local news and local officials and
athletes. Formula One race car drivers, for example, because I don't follow basketball
players because they're usually just talking about how flat the earth is. You know, I don't
know where Mastodon's going to fall down on that. I do know that it has been increasing
very rapidly. I think in the past week it gained 300,000 more people. I think it's up
over 8 million people, which is small compared to Twitter, but it's early days of the Twitter
exodus.
I think that the reason basketball players think that the world is flat is because they never leave the basketball court and those are generally flat.
I think that they're so busy always. They've spent so many millions of hours of their lives holding a round object that they're just sick of it.
Being round, yeah.
Yeah, being round. Yeah, it just drives them insane.
There's got to be more to a round thing, yeah.
And in their dreams it haunts them and they say, "Damn you, round thing! I will have flatness all around me!"
Uh-oh, Peter's leaving.
He's doing a remote control on something.
I don't know what's happening. I feel scared. What if Peter's having a stroke? Oh, he's trying to control something in his house
No, what I was trying to do was get enough light so that I could read the label because I can never remember the name
Which there are two beer companies. I like one is Burlington beer company and the other is Burlington brewery
Brewing a Burlington brewing company my god. Can we just have them have a cave match?
Well, one's Burlington, Massachusetts. The other's Burlington, Vermont. This is Burlington Beer Company out of Vermont and
I am about to open up Study Hall.
Study Hall is a maple coffee amber ale.
Sounds really good. It is. Now, it's not as good as mochaccino.
I still have mochaccino one left from the four-pack in my refrigerator from almost a year ago.
Which you've never sent me one of those and I can't get them here. Because it's the last one.
And I haven't been able to find them this year. I haven't seen that they're actually selling them anywhere yet. But anyway
Study Hall is much lighter. It's five point five percent alcohol. So I'm gonna pop one of these guys right now
I mean the mochaccino one was basically a dessert with some alcohol poured into it
Oh is amazing, but it was only it was a nice seven percent alcohol, which is a nice sweet spot between
week four and
overbearing nine point eight
Which means you will fall down the stairs, but you'll catch yourself on the last step before you crash and die
Pretty much, but not with a study hall. Now. I just have to say one thing
There's no study hall that I'm aware of that would accept you drinking that in it
Adult colleges remote learning I mean hey Cheers Trump University
Hey, maybe yay can start his own University
Yay, since apparently he's out of jobs now everyone's dumped him his he doesn't have an agent. He doesn't have his contracts anymore
Apparently people don't like it when you say I like Hitler when you literally say the words. I like Hitler
Huh Nazis probably would
Hmm you'd think right, but they're not funding any
hip-hop artists I
Suppose that's possible
Well, what else is going on? I have to say I'm glad there's no Nazi rap that I'm aware
Actually, there probably is if I probably have supremacy subcultures
I would probably find I don't know if I would or not. I don't want it's not look
Let's not go looking for for that. All right, Peter, you have something here called counterculture
Slow-motion, what is that all about? That's something I'm not yet drinking. So stop. Oh, I'm sorry
Oh, I didn't know it was a drink. It sounded like a social movement
Yeah, no, Counter Culture, I have drunk Counter Culture on this podcast before, I think, is
a brewing company, but I haven't gotten to that yet.
Well, I'm the guy that makes the JSON file with all the beers in it, and I don't remember
that one, but let me go to friendswithbrews.com and type-
Maybe I haven't actually drunk it yet, but I did buy it with the intention of drinking
it on the podcast.
Yeah, you haven't had it on this podcast.
Because the last time we recorded it was in late afternoon and I did not want to be up
late.
So that's why I've just gone to a beer route right now instead of the second cup of coffee.
Although the coffee that I was planning on drinking today, as you can probably guess
by the name, it's called Slow Motion.
It's a decaf.
Ah, yeah, that's definitely Slow Motion.
Okay, let me talk one last thing about something related to Mastodon and then I'll get over
myself.
You and Adam were talking about Mastodon apps very briefly.
You weren't talking about them as much as you were talking about not having really tried
any of them.
Ooh, I just mentioned a couple that were mentioned.
Most of them are fairly not good, I must say.
Yep.
Not real polished in the UI department.
But the people who make Tweetbot, a company called Tapbots, they now have an app called
Ivory that is in beta, and I am on the beta, which unfortunately is full right now.
But anyway, they're working on their own Mastodon app and they're going to make a Mac version
and they, yeah, it's in progress.
And let me just say, it's nice.
I like it.
Even Siracusa hasn't gotten his beta yet.
No, he was very outraged.
How do you get your beta?
You have to be like, is it invite only?
It was just timing.
I saw someone, I literally was on Mastodon.
I saw someone say something about it and I'm like, Oh, how'd you get on that?
And he's, and after I asked that, I found, I saw the link.
I went there, I got my test flight real quick.
And then next thing I knew other people were already not being able to get it.
It just filled up really fast.
Got it.
So now I believe they could increase that limit if they wanted to, but maybe they don't
want to.
Maybe they're trying to plan for capacity.
Siracusa I was asking, John Chidgey was asking, people were asking for exceptions, but as
far as I know, Tapbots hasn't responded to any of them.
Okay.
But what I'm saying is it's a nice app.
If you try some of the current existing ones and you're like, Oh my God, this is not the
most handsome app I've ever seen. Don't worry, there's a pretty polished looking and nice
to use app on the way. Look, I hate to say that because it sounds very dismissive of
people who have been making apps way before Tapbots decided to come in and grace the world
with their app. And I get that they're probably frustrated, but the fact of the matter is
most of those apps are nowhere near as polished in the UI department. And it does make a difference.
It just does, you know?
It just does.
Mm-hmm.
So I'm sorry.
Okay.
Yeah, I don't think you have to be sorry.
Well, I've had conversations with people.
And they feel more sorry for the other app developers, and I get it, but no matter who
you are, when you use software, or you use any other product for that matter, you are
gonna pick the one that seems the nicest for you and does the job for you and meets all
things that you expect in a nice product of whatever category. And that's how you choose.
Unless you're stuck at work using whatever crap they give you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. But what I'm saying is you can't expect people not to use the apps that seem more
polished and look nicer than the other ones. You just can't expect it. It's just not realistic.
And I look, I'm a horrible designer. I totally get, you know, if I designed a Mastodon app,
it would be ugly too. But I wouldn't get frustrated and bitter and say, oh,
those guys just come blowing in here and all of a sudden everybody's worshiping them.
I would say, well, their app looks pretty good. And mine, honestly, it looks a little bit like,
you know, I would just have to be honest about it. I mean, that that's honesty. That's refreshing,
honesty, refreshing, like your, how is your, so now talk about your beer. So it is, it is,
You know, it's an amber ale which I generally tend to like and there are notes of coffee in it
So I think that's the study hall, you know, like you're studying so you're drinking coffee
Because if there's coffee in your beer, there's no way your study session is gonna go wrong
No matter how much of you drink
one of my classmates in college said that the trick if you were gonna be drinking while you were
programming or if you're gonna be drinking while studying
You needed to be at the same level of inebriation when you took the test.
I never actually tried that, but I am somewhat skeptical about that as a strategy.
Okay, I wouldn't try it either, but I will say that it makes complete sense if two things here.
Number one, the initial level of abbreabbreviation.
[laughs]
Help me, Peter.
Inebriation.
I was going to say, I wanted to stick with abbreviation. I like that.
If the initial level of abbreviation is such that you can still actually study and retain some things,
and then assuming that you actually can get to that exact same level or close enough and maintain it throughout the test,
those are two very hard to meet conditions.
My recommendation would be that the level of inebriation be sober.
Right, it'd be zero, yes. Zero abbreviations. Yeah, that's my recommendation. Zero inebriations.
What it says to me is your previous classmate had a bit of a drinking problem, and they were
trying to find a way to not have to not drink and yet still succeed at exams.
Huh, drinking problem in college, hmm.
And because they thought that they were applying a scientific approach to it,
somehow it justified everything?
Uh, probably.
And I think they're probably wrong.
Do you think they're dead now?
Have you followed up with this person in the last 20 years?
I have not actually.
I have not.
I think they're dead.
So, yeah.
Yeah.
So, so, so what are these?
So you're talking tweetbot, cause you put like ivory and obsidian and things.
Ivory.
Yeah.
I've ivory is the beta app.
It's the beta massive on app by the people that make Tweetbot.
Okay.
Which is probably the most popular third party Twitter client.
So what I'm saying is probably some of our listeners will know who they are.
I doubt that we have listeners that don't know who they are.
However, we may have I don't know what our demographic of 10 listeners is.
I don't know if some of them are on Android and they don't use iOS.
So they may not know what tweetbot or tapbots is.
Well, there could be tens of listeners even, you know, maybe not more than 10.
But I also expect that people that are willing to put up with Android are
probably willing to put up with Twitter anyway.
So there you go.
Probably.
I'm back to firing our listeners, Peter.
Yay.
Good job.
We had too many anyway.
I know it's going too well.
What is the English?
The English Peter is a TV show on Amazon Prime and it is an Old West show.
Oh, I think I've heard about that.
It's really good.
I didn't expect to like it but it primarily follows two people.
One is an English woman who comes to America to... well, I'm not 100% sure why she's there
yet.
She's there for vengeance and she might also be there to find a guy who used to be her
her fiance, but then he went to America and terrible things happened and he decided to
stay there so that he wouldn't destroy her life as well as his. But it follows her and
it follows an Indian who was in, I keep thinking, I keep wanting to say US Army, but it wasn't
the US Army. Anyway, it was a US military outfit that was fighting against the Indians
and other, well, yeah, basically against the Indians because who else was there really?
But anyway, the reason he did it is because these Indian tribes were already fighting
each other, right?
And so he figured the enemy of my enemies, so he joined up.
He also had a lot of terrible things happen.
The other reason he did it is because everybody in his family was already killed, pretty much.
And it follows him coming to terms with what he's done and what it means and what his relationship
with other people in a world where the white people are clearly coming in and decimating
all of Indian, all of American Indians, Native Americans. They call them Indians in the movie,
that's why I keep in the TV show, of course, because it's period appropriate, that's what
they call them. That's why I'm using the word Indian here, because I'm talking about what the
show says. He's dealing with a lot of stuff, she's dealing with a lot of stuff, and they kind of wind
up saving each other's lives several times throughout the show because, my god, what a
lawless play. It really captures the lawlessness of the West and what people will do to survive
and not just survive, but to eke out a profit in a place where it's really hard to make
a living. There's a lot of people that you don't mind seeing die. Let's put it that way.
Do you ever watch Deadwood on HBO? No, no. I thought it was excellent. And yeah, I've
heard that it was. I'm just not an HBO guy. Sounds familiar. Sounds, sounds similar. But
But the guy who plays the...
I can't even remember what tribe he was from now.
Probably because of this tribe of beer that I'm drinking, but...
I just hiccuped in your honor.
He is amazingly compelling.
He is super, super compelling.
And it's just a really good show.
I really, really recommend it.
Emily Blunt is the actress who plays the English woman.
She's good.
And I can't remember his name, but he's an interesting character.
He didn't actually become super successful in acting until into his 40s.
He had a lot of drug and alcohol problems, and he finally got clean right before he got
a big breakthrough role, and then now he's doing this and he's got some other projects
going.
But the way he plays the part is really, really compelling.
And it just makes for a good show because there is a lot of conflict in what he's doing,
even though, yeah, his tribe is enemies with other tribes.
Does that justify him going to war against them?
And the fact that is that he's helping the people who are also decimating him along with
the other Indians.
It's really fascinating.
And the good thing is it's not just a bunch of action of people getting killed, although
there's plenty of that.
It's the storyline and the characters and the really good acting that really make it
a show worth watching.
Okay.
It's about the people.
I mean, so I haven't been into westerns as much.
I haven't either. That's why it took me a long time to get to watching it.
Recently.
Yeah.
I used to be, I was much bigger, even recently I was bigger into westerns like last year
when I would be playing and running games of Deadlands, which is essentially cowboys
and weird west cowboys and zombies version of like Dungeons and Dragons if you're familiar
at all with D&D. It's like that.
So I was doing lots of different, watching all of my favorite Westerns and things to
get in the mood.
But what you're describing sounds right up that alley.
Yeah, I started losing interest in Westerns right about the time the Bundys took over
the Bureau of Land Management in Oregon and were protesting about their rights and all
that stuff.
I kind of started losing patience with people on the east side of the state, let's put it
that way.
I'm sorry, it's just the truth.
In other news, I'm drinking this beer and it is very wheaty and something that I have
noticed in relatively low alcohol, wheaty beers. They make me somewhat congested. They
make my nose get a little bit stuffy. Something, a phenomenon I have noticed that I first noticed
I think earlier this year, maybe the spring or so this one is doing it to me. According
to the show notes, that won't be a problem because nothing can come out of your nose.
Well, it is a problem because as you just alluded I
Two days ago just had my nose
Cauterized the blood vessels in my left nostril because I tend to get frequent nosebleeds
Especially this time of year. Okay, I guess so I saw a doctor and he was great. I really liked it
You know, he went and stuffed the hot poker right up my nose and sealed that thing up shut
I was gonna ask you what did they just heat up a soldering iron and go here you go
Pretty much. No, what they do is, you know, he diagnosed it and he says, yeah, you have a really big blood vessel running down your left vein, your right vein, however, it's nice and open and it's even concave. I'm like, okay, if you say so.
This guy's infatuated with your right vein.
He's a doctor. It's what he does.
Yeah, but it sounds like he's in love a little bit.
So he, uh, first he applied some topical numbing agent, which actually the worst part about it was
that it just tasted terrible because you know, some of it goes down your nose into, into your
throat. Right. But he was able to like, you know, zap it up and cauterize it pretty well.
And then as he discharges me, he says, yeah, don't, uh, you know, here are things you can't do
for five days. And the list of things that I can't do for five days includes blowing my nose.
Oh my god.
It's gross. And here I'm like, I'm snorting and getting ready like, oh, I'd like, I also am not
supposed to insert anything into my nose. So I can't like poke around it to like, you know,
manually like sop like osmosis, you know, the mucus out of it or anything. It's like,
it's really gross and now I'm starting to get, oh I'm also not supposed to inhale sharply so I
can't even like snort it up and try to spit it out. It's not a great place to be right now.
Basically you can't use your nose. Pretty much, yeah. And it was hilarious because yesterday the
first thing I signed into my early morning yoga class yesterday morning, the first thing that the
instructor says like we're gonna start by inhaling sharply and then slowly exhaling. I was like,
I'll see you next week.
You didn't have to do that. You could still do the yoga and just breathe your own way.
Yeah, I know. I was being being facetious.
But yeah, I got my nose cauterized after dealing with like rampant chronic nosebleeds for decades.
I'm really hopeful that this will, you know, stop it. Although the doctor said this isn't, he alluded to the fact
that's not a permanent fix.
that's more of a temporary fix because he said, you know, like you should be good for a few months.
Sure. I have a very American question to ask you. Is this considered a cosmetic procedure,
Peter, and your insurance will not cover it? Or is this considered a vital and necessary procedure
and your insurance will cover it? I am not sure. I did get referred and they asked if I had insurance.
Right. I would think that stopping bleeding would be important enough to be covered,
but then again, tampons are apparently considered a luxury item. And let's be honest, you're probably
not going to bleed to death from this and it's just unsightly for you and for everyone else,
therefore it's a cosmetic issue. I'm kind of curious. I don't know. We'll find out.
I'd be amazed if they didn't try to blow it off as some unnecessary... They did ask. I mean,
they did ask what my insurance was at the doctor's office so that implies that insurance might be
covered so we shall see insurance in america is a weird thing oh my god from a record okay well i
was curious about that because uh uh i was showing vicar show notes and he was like what's the
cauterized thing he he was very alarmed by that and i said i don't know maybe it's a sinus thing
i didn't know what it was yeah no but what do you see he numbed it up and then he had a little thing
I'm presuming it was a hot poker and stuff, you know, just like a needle sized thing and he just kind of like
Yeah, soldering arc. I felt a little bit of a pinch, you know, it was the pain was very manageable those
It was it was mostly it was it was very uncomfortable, but it wasn't painful
The good news was I didn't smell anything. That was my concern. I thought I was gonna cuz literally hot in nose
I'm thinking
Burning flesh within the say, you know because that was the weird thing when I had laser eye surgery when I had LASIK
I could smell the eyes getting toasted. It was bizarre.
Are you sure? What year did you have this done? Because when I had LASIK I couldn't, I couldn't. I could see the flaps go up.
I could see them flip the flap up.
That was weird too. That was weird because you have to keep it open.
Yeah, keep it open and then I could see it flip back down, but I couldn't smell anything.
I smelled it and it was bizarre. It was like 20 years ago.
Yeah, I'm trying to remember when mine was mine was quite a long time ago now to actually
Probably approaching 20 years as well
The place I went to they were pretty advanced they were using equipment that not everybody had yet at the time
So I don't know okay. Maybe it was the smell remover. Maybe they had a
super silent vacuum sucking away the smell that I
See you here. Giant sucking sound. Giant sucking sound. Here, hold on. Now what we're gonna do is flip your eye open
No, it wasn't I would not go to that guy
Don't do it. Well, I'm glad that your nose is cauterized, I guess.
Well, actually, I'm more glad that you made it through.
And I will be curious to see if it helps with the nosebleeds.
I have to say, I haven't really noticed a lot of nose bleeding on this podcast.
But... No, not today, which is great.
But, you know, it's just like, ehh.
Has this ever happened at work where you're just sitting there talking with the people and all of a sudden you're like, "Oh my God, is my nose bleeding?"
On rare occasions, it just happens.
The most embarrassing times that it happened, most inconvenient times, was twice it happened while I was at a restaurant.
And like at the dinner table, all of a sudden I'm like, "sniff, sniff, touch, oh $--t, I have to excuse myself," and I'm gone for like literally 15 minutes.
Right, right.
It also happened once at a yoga class. Like right off the bat, the very first pose, my friend and teacher Sharon says, "Hey, we're gonna start in downward dog."
And as soon as I invert and go into the first downward dog
I see red drops on my mat and I was in the in the bathroom for about 15 minutes
Waiting for that one to stop. She's like, I'm sorry Peter. That's bloody downward dog. We're not doing that here bloody downward dog
But no what what I don't like is
What's interesting is a different thing first. What's interesting is though is I have like two types of nosebleeds
One is like just you know, just a spot
I can hear a sniff sniff touch a Kleenex to it and then it's done and then there's like a gusher and
I don't know like maybe it's you know, my heart rate, you know blood pressure is up and it's really pumping
But when it when that happens like nothing I do will stop it
The only thing I can do is wait it out and it's really really sucks
How often does that happen often enough that I was like?
Getting borderline losing my temper and it's like what am I supposed to get angry at my own nose?
You know like it was but it was really inconvenient and it sucked so I have a really
Stupid question would it help to have something that you could shove up the left nostril?
But I did I mean I would shove like, you know a clean
I mean before I would hold up and so go out that day with something shoved high up high enough that people won't see it
Well, that's the thing. It can't be that high because it's relatively low in the nostril where it happens
So you're gonna see something but even then there's no predicting it right, you know
Like I'd have to wear this every freaking day. So yeah, I don't know. Glad we had that conversation
Yeah, I thought when you were talking about health problems, I thought we were gonna talk about your knee or something
How is your knee doing?
so
It sounds like I have a partially torn meniscus ouch. I had physical therapy yesterday
I've had my third third session was yesterday
And my PT and this is the same guy who I saw last year after my stress fracture in my foot
yeah, he
Was to you know, said asked me like so you got any big races come planned and I'm like, well
I'm running the dairy cheap in April. I'm hoping to is it? Oh, yeah
I was gonna run that and yeah blah blah, but you know, I'm gonna do Boston next year
I just I'm just gonna take it easy and stuff
But what he did not do was give me the sideways glance or say I don't think you want to be planning to do
That so I took that as a good sign that you know, he doesn't seem overly concerned that you know
About me doing a doing a marathon in April
So we'll see we'll see I am planning I'm gonna be taking a vacation
Soon or I'm gonna be gone for a month in between that time which is gonna be cool
But you know, we'll see I'm hoping to be you know practicing or you know training and stuff while I'm gone
Because I deliberately Gardner or something anything that gets me anything that allows me to go live with you for a month. I
Have guest rooms in both of the places that I'm renting in Costa Rica, right?
But I need to get paid because I can't afford right now. Well, Costa Rica is really cheap
I know but my daughter's going on a trip to Japan, which is not really cheap and that's awesome
But you could work, you could work, you could do your remote work from where we're going to be, right?
So as long as you don't have to go onsite and someone else is going to have to pick her up from school too.
That's kind of a bummer.
I'll have to see if my boss will hire an assistant for me so that they can do the onsite work while I'm gone.
Do that. Do that and then come on down.
I'm actually due for a sabbatical. I could take a sabbatical. I could take a two month sabbatical anytime I want right now.
Does it have to do you have to take the whole two months?
Or can you take it in pieces?
I don't think I do. But if I was going to go somewhere, I would definitely take the whole
two months. And then what I would do is go somewhere. And then I would spend the majority
of that with my family. That's the that's the only reason I've really been waiting is to figure
out when's a good time for my family, which sucks because there is no good time right now because
we're still coming out of the tail end of a pandemic. And we're also not super flush with
cash right now. So my wife's working a lot and then, you know, my daughter's, I don't
know, it's just, I don't know what I'm going to do. But anyway, what I'm saying is you're
tempting me to try to figure out a way to spend a week or two of that elsewhere.
I think you should. I think you should. So what I did is I rented two Airbnbs and one
is closer to the beach and one is closer in the mountains, in the woods.
So you'd probably stuff me in the woods and then you'd go to the beach. Is that what you're
saying?
Sure. Let's do that. My plan was to do running though, you know, like to be running in the
woods, you know, a lot of trail running and stuff. And apparently it's a, you know, a
safe part of the country, safe neighborhoods, et cetera. It's still, you know, central America.
It's not going to be United States, but you know, they, it's not Brazil. So apparently
it's like a giant playground from the way people are describing it. But then again,
people that I've talked to all, you know, like would go to resorts and stay in these,
you know, like walled in hotel package deal kind of things.
Right. Cause I was going to say, I think there, cause I've had friends that are like photographers
and stuff and I'm pretty sure there are places there where you don't want to go with like
your camera gear and stuff. Could be. I mean, I plan, you know, like when I'm out, I'm probably
gonna have my phone on me, my Apple watch and not a lot else. Passport, I don't know.
I don't even know right now what the recommended best practice is. Are you supposed to keep
your passport with you to prove who you are or do you leave it home? Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know what the best practice is.
Hey, do these BnBs have, do these places have safes in them so you can put your MacBook
in your...
Thinking about that, I don't know that they do. That's a very good question.
I think we should get one.
But I might at least bring a little security camera along, you know, at least as a backup.
I think both of the places that I'm going to have security cameras on on-prem as well.
I'm not 100% sure though now. I don't have to think about it.
Because not only would you be wildly inconvenienced if your laptop, let's say, went missing,
you would also be screwed because you're presumably going to be doing some work
during that period of time.
Yeah. Oh yeah. No, I am planning. I'll definitely take some time off. Um,
but in general, this is just a relocation, not a vacation as much.
So yeah. Yeah. But I might end up just like, you know what,
I'm taking a freaking week off, whatever.
Well, I'm gonna, let me just put it this way. I will,
I will at least have the idea that maybe I should think about it as a,
somewhat not certain, but also not impossible possibility.
An impossible impossibility.
That maybe I would go down there for at least a few days
or a week or whatever.
Well, I have extended the invitation to Adam and his wife.
It doesn't work with their vacation schedule.
They're going to be going to other places.
I have extended it to four other people
and all of them are like, yeah, that sounds amazing.
I can't do it.
Right.
So, so far, it's I've got the place to myself.
I'm like, all right, you know, it's gonna be just me and going out and having fun.
Then that's totally cool.
That's pretty amazing, honestly.
It might be exactly what you need.
There you go.
This is the perfect time to get your nose cauterized.
That way you won't go sauntering into a bar down there and...
Yeah.
That would be less than optimal.
But the short answer though is, but the knee seems to be doing very well.
It's constantly stiff.
And today I was just thinking, the only thing that hurts it though, that aggravates and
causes pain is like external rotation.
Like think pigeon pose.
That's what causes the pain.
And then today when I was walking in my living room, like with the foot planted, I turned
to the right and that torquing motion triggered it.
Not terribly, but it hurt a little bit. So my thought is, when I was running this summer,
on almost every long run, at some point during the run, I would trip and fall. It was always my left
foot getting caught on something. And when I thought about it, the difference between, like,
my left foot naturally pronates inward, whereas my right foot naturally supinates outward.
Oh my God, you're running sideways all the time.
Exactly. Literally. So I had to deliberately crank things back. And as soon as I put, like,
focused my attention on that, in addition to all the other things when I'm trail running,
I stopped falling. As long as I would keep my attention and I could almost, I couldn't even
make myself trip over something like when I would try, like going over a rock or a root or something.
So I fixed that problem. My suspicion is that I was overcompensating.
Yeah, that's what I was... or even if you weren't overcompensating, it's a change.
It is a change, but that external rotation is the same motion that I felt with that foot planted and
then turning to the right. So I'm thinking that's probably what's going on. Even if it wasn't over
compensation, let's say you were actually picking an angle that would work well and wasn't
unreasonable. It's just a change and you're not reducing your mileage or working into it in any
So it definitely causes strain.
Right. But I mean, it didn't manifest until like three, four months later.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
But you know, these things, but that gives credit to like, they exactly,
they built up and that's probably what happened.
I have a news for you. The older you get,
the easier it's going to be to injure yourself in that type of way.
Like where you can tell that, oh my God,
I just did something way too many times, you know,
After a million times of doing this one thing my body is angry. I believe that's called an RSI right repetitive strain injury
It's a lot easier to do that kind of thing without knowing that it's happening
mm-hmm all of a sudden you'll just be in severe pain and
It sucks because
Overdo stuff without having any freaking clue that you're overdoing it because you feel great at the time
Feels fine feels fine feels fine all of a sudden. Oh my god
Well, I probably need to start giving more attention to what's called prehab as opposed to rehab
You know and start doing these exercises and you know things like that
I've got I've got two good physical therapists that I'm working with and I don't know if they're both runners
I don't know if the lady is but the guy he definitely he's like yeah, I got into Boston for next year
But I'm gonna delay it. I'm gonna do it in 2024 and I did two marathons last year
I'm like, okay, these are my people he knows what I'm going through
He's probably like, you know, closer to half my age, but still he knows what, you know,
he's also a doctorate of PT.
So he knows what I'm going through and he's a runner.
So I'm happy.
You know, what's funny is my PT guy that I just, I've only seen him one time, but I just
started going for my rotator cuff.
Yeah.
And he is, at first when I saw him, I thought he was half my age.
After I, we were both wearing masks of course, cause it's a medical facility.
After I interacted with him a little bit and I was looking, you know, got a better sense
of his face and could see some of the wrinkles around his eyes and stuff. He's probably not
half my age, but he's definitely younger than me, and the funny thing is he has a daughter
the same age as mine, which cracks me up. It always cracks me up when friends of mine,
their kids were graduating from high school about the time that my daughter was learning
about the color yellow in kindergarten or whatever. But anyway, but this guy, he seems
like he could definitely be a marathoner. He's got that build and he definitely, he,
I think he is definitely a yoga guy because I was telling him that one of my he's like
what are you trying to you know what's your end expectation from this because he's telling
me you might not come out of this 100% pain free you might not come out of this a lot
and I said that's fine I already have other existing pains that I have to monitor and
keep track of but they don't stop me from doing what I need to do and they don't get
worse from me doing those things they're just kind of there I said if my shoulders that
way but I can do my full range of motion during yoga and other activities that's
the kind of thing that I'm looking for okay he's like that's a realistic
expectation but he does seem to have a pretty good idea of yoga and he was you
know he likes the fact that I'm doing yoga and stuff like that so I I have a
feeling that working with him will be pretty good well I was gonna ask you I
was like wait so you you think he's into yoga because he tells you you might not
come out of this pain-free that's a weird conclusion no no no he's because
he'd know he understands when I'm describing the different yoga poses and
what which way I need to rotate my arm in order to be able to do the pose and
stuff like that I get that I mean a lot of no he's just he's just trying to be
realistic he's saying that having suffered this injury and having had this
pain you're probably never gonna get to the point where you don't feel like this
ever happened yep when I had my rotator cuff surgery my doctor that the surgeon
told me that, you know, it's not going to be a hundred percent. And I disagree. I think
he got me back to what I think was a hundred percent.
But see, I think the difference is, well, that is actually pretty amazing and that's
great.
Yeah.
Might even be unusual. I don't know.
Well, of course he seemed to think so. Well, you have to factor in though, maybe it was
the fact that I had been at so suboptimal for so long that that's why it seemed like 100% you know
that could be you also had surgery whereas all I'm going to do is physical therapy to build up
the muscles in such a way that hopefully my arms won't basically you're compensating for a
particular weak spot right and there is no plan to have surgery because mine aren't that bad mine's
It's not that bad. It's not as bad as yours were. In fact, you know,
he does the strength test where they tell you to hold your arms at different
angles and they press on them and try to see if you can maintain without,
you know, and he said, your arms are basically the same strength.
I can't tell any difference. So it's not like it's a super bad injury. Yeah,
that's a good sign. It's just very painful in certain positions.
And so I guess what I'm saying is because I'm not going to have anything
massively interventional, like a surgery,
I wouldn't be surprised if it probably is true that while it's not as bad to begin with,
the overall outcome might not be as super good as yours, where I have no pain that I
notice anymore.
Yeah.
I mean, that said, it did come back, you know, over time, and it did degrade mostly due to
working out with a teenager in a jiu-jitsu class, and, you know, the kid had no proprioception
and was wailing on my shoulder after I had already submitted to, you know, through the hold.
So that was one of my last jiu-jitsu classes.
Yeah. And then you couldn't go back there because you killed the kid.
I did not kill the kid.
All right. Well, we have been going for an hour now.
We have.
And I didn't talk about Obsidian. Let's talk about it next time. But I do want to talk about it
because I think you might find it very interesting.
I don't think that Obsidian is a direct Evernote replacement for you
because it's not a filing cabinet.
But what it is, is a very fascinating organizational tool
that can be scripted in different ways.
And it's got lots of different powerful plugins
that you can get data from your notes
and present it to yourself in different ways.
It's really, really cool.
And I'm using it both for myself now,
like for all the notes I take for servers, for podcasts, for anything.
And I'm also using it for work now. I started using it for work because I noticed with stuff in OneNote,
there are a lot of times I just drop the ball on something because it's there in OneNote somewhere,
but it doesn't surface to me and I don't... anyway.
This makes it a lot easier to make sure stuff gets surfaced to you.
And so, anyway, we'll talk about it at some future date, but I think you might find it interesting.
All right. I'm, you know, I was here interested to hear about new tech options.
Obsidian is one of those things that air free buddy has been talking about.
When you say everybody, who does that include?
Mac communities that I listened to. Okay. I was just curious because you're everybody does not
obviously interact with my everybody. Cause I'd never heard of it until you know what I take that
Beck, my godson might have mentioned that. He told me about this awesome note-taking app that
he was using and I don't have it in my shortcuts, in my reminders. Well, the two that everybody are
talking about, there's one called Craft, which I could not stand and my wife and I tried it and
we were like, this is dumb. And then there's Obsidian, which is very powerful and allows
you to customize and program against it. I think that's the one he told me about also.
I kind of was against it. I'm one of those people that when everybody is raving about something,
I'm kind of contrarian. But then at Thanksgiving, my brother showed me how he's using it. And I was
like, "Okay, now that is cool. Now I get it. Now I understand why I would use this." And so it was
really having my brother with his Mac there at Thanksgiving, bring it over and show me exactly
how he was using it and what he was doing and some of the plugins. And I was like, "Okay,
Now I'm on board and now I'm deep into it. Okay. All right. Like I said, like as you said though,
yeah, I am using it. I use Evernote really as a, you know, a filing cabinet because, you know,
again, it's basically endless storage, you know, for my purpose. That said, I have no idea how much
space I'm really using in Evernote. I haven't done a massive export in a long time. It's probably not
even an issue. It's probably, you know, like, oh yeah, one gig you're done. Yeah. So yeah. My,
My godson did tell me about obsidian. Yeah, so what you might do is talk to him and then
don't think of it as will I use this instead of Evernote. Think of this as will this help
improve my organization and my planning and my information. Stuff that I need to work with all
the time will it will it improve that part of my life. Got it. More than just here's something I
might need some time and it could be any type of file and I want to dump it in a cabinet.
I don't think they're equivalent that way, but I do think that it's super great at being able to...
Like, for example, let's say I have a folder and I've got a bunch of subfolders, and I can do simple
things like have a top-level page that says, "Just show me the index page and all those things."
I can write a query against that with something called Data View, and then on those subfolders,
I can have their own index pages and I can show me a list of all the nodes. And not just lists,
but you can do table views, you can do Kanban boards, you can do all kinds of stuff. And querying
by tag, querying by page title, querying by... It's almost like being able to do SQL queries against
notes. Yeah, that sounds really cool. That sounds really cool. And again, as you said,
my Evernote usage is I just throw stuff in there and in excess of 99% of the time, I just forget
about it and that's it. And you know, but many times I have gone back in and I was just like,
yep, I needed that. That was, that was, I'm, you know, the, yep, I'm glad I have it there,
you know? So yeah, it makes sense. It can't hurt to have it. And so like,
this won't replace my use of Apple Notes because Apple Notes is more similar to what Evernote is.
And it's stuff that I share with my wife and where documents, receipts,
little bits of information here and there. And she's, Hey,
she's never going to use Obsidian and B I just don't see it as the equivalent
use case. Right. And so, but yeah, we'll, we'll talk about it next time.
Maybe.
Cool. I'll put it in the future topics to be addressed.
Well, on that note, maybe we should wrap this episode,
put a pin in it, you know, ever note, stick a stick a fork in it.
It's done or something like that
Stick your mastodon trunk
To this tell your friends tell your friends. What are we supposed to tell our friends? I don't know
Oh, I know what you're supposed to tell your friends
I
Didn't even hear that. I don't do not know what I'm supposed to tell my friends
Said get away from the computer. Oh
Then all the hacker sound clips are very bad. Here's another one
You have a zero bug attack and all lock in an overlay file run antivirus zero bug
Now I want to watch hackers and actually, you know what? I want to watch war games again
That's what I want to watch war games is really cheesy. But yeah, it's not bad
I guess some of those movies definitely don't hold up. No, no cool. Well on that note, let's let's let's rock it. Let's rock it
My button is orange, but I'll press it. Anyway, boom kill it big orange button
Big orange...